

AIRLANGGA YUDIATAMA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT



Whatsapp

+62 812 8481 7372



mail

airlangga.yudiatama@outlook.com

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Airlangga you can call me "air" or "angga". I'm a Software Engineer and I can be a Fullstack Developer too.

I have been years in programming I specialize focused in Backend Python or Java, I care deeply about build Microservice and Integration.

SOCIAL MEDIA



Github

github.com/airgg



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/airlangga-yudiatama



Website

airgg.netlify.app

EDUCATION

JAKARTA STATE POLYTECHNIC

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING: 2020 - 2024

CCIT - FACULTY OF ENGINEERING UNIVERSITY OF INDONESIA

COMPUTER SCIENCE: 2020 - 2022

SMKN 1 CIBINONG

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING: 2017 - 2020

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

CONVERSATIONAL

INDONESIAN

FLUENT

AWARDS

2023

- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Hackathon).
- Web Developer Competency Professional Certification (LSP Jakarta State Polytechnic).

2022

- Programmer Competency Professional Certification (LSP University of Indonesia)
- Student Creativity Program: PKM (Finalist Pass Funding).
- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Best Poster).

SKILLS

PYTHON



JAVASCRIPT



JAVA

FLUTTER



MISC

CORELDRAW



РНОТОЅНОР



FIGMA

3

EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP

PT ELANG MAHKOTA TEKNOLOGI TBK. | AUG - DEC 2023

LEAD FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

DEPOK CITY HEALTH DEPARTMENT | MAY 2023 - SEP 2023

AIRLANGGA YUDIATAMA

airlangga.yudiatama@outlook.com | +6281284817372 | linkedin.com/airlangga-yudiatama github.com/airgg | airgg.github.io | Bogor, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

About

Hello my name is Angga, I am a Fullstack Developer with over five years of experience in building web applications and more than two years of experience developing mobile applications using Java and Flutter. I specialize in backend development, utilizing Python, JavaScript, and Java as my primary programming languages. My expertise extends to modern frameworks such as FastAPI, Flask, and Django for Python, and React.js, Vue.js, and their respective frameworks (Next.js, Nuxt.js) for JavaScript/TypeScript.

Experience

PT Elang Mahkota Teknologi Tbk.

Internship Fullstack Developer. Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

- Developed a website to monitor the status of IoT (Internet of Things) devices integration with sensor for doing remote procedure call. This website for monitoring and visualization data telemetri from sensor IoT.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, NuxtJS, VueJS, PostgreSQL (Web)

Depok City Health Department

Project Based Learning - Community Service. May 2023 - Sep 2023

- Developed the simkesling website, this website is for hospital and puskesmas waste management and data collection of transporters who transport the waste as a report.
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, NextJS, ReactJS, MySQL (Web)

PT Fedora Cakra Informatika

Freelance Android Developer. Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

- Developed Apps with login multi user. This apps is for create queue and check queue, see doctor's schedule, room information, emergency call and see the location of the hospital and deployed for three hospital in Makassar, Sumatera and West Java.
- Tools: Dart, Flutter, Rest API (Android)

PT Bank Pembiayaan Rakyat Syariah Dinar Ashri

Freelance Fullstack Developer, Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

- Developed Web E-Collateral with login multi user, multi level and deployed in multi branch company. This web is for management inventory and location collateral of bank customer.
- · Tools: Python, FastApi, VueJS, PostgreSQL (Web)

Depok City Health Department

Project Based Learning - Community Service. Jul 2022 - Aug 2022

- Developed Web Lalapan Depok with login multi user and multi level. This web for Online Food Safe Training Class, so the food handlers and drinking water depots in the city of Depok can get a certificate Food Sanitation Hygiene (HSP).
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL (Web)

Bank Pembangunan Daerah: BPD Yogyakarta

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

- Develope Web for Rekonsal and Reversal Transaction PPOB. This web is like tools for supporting main PPOB Banking Application BPD Yogya.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, VueJS, SQLite (Web)

Koperasi Usaha Putera Pribumi: KUPP

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

- Developed Web Tracking Taxi Airport Soekarno-Hatta with multi login user and multi level. This web for manage driver, car, transaction integration with Google Maps and Firebase for Realtime detect driver and report.
- Developed Apps Tracking Taxi Airport with login multi user. This apps for driver to get order, for the driver states ready and Realtime tracking where the driver is.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, VueJS, SQLite, Firebase (Web) | Flutter, SQLite, Firebase (Android)

Kementerian Kelautan dan Perikanan: KKP

Freelance Android Developer. Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

- Developed Apps Lautku with login multi user and multi level. This apps for trainer upload new video and user for buying video and view video.
- Tools: Python, Flask, VueJS, MySQL (Web) | Flutter, MySQL, SQLite (Android)

Overpast Experience

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Jun 2019 - Aug 2021

• I have 3 other industry experience with more than 1 year. Stacks: Java, Spring, Python, Flask, Javascript, VueJS, SQLServer, MySQL.

Educations _

Jakarta State Polythechnic (Bachelor Degree). GPA 3.62. Informatics Engineering. 2020 - 2024.

CCIT - Faculty of Engineering, University of Indonesia (Associate Degree). GPA 3.64. Computer Science. 2020 - 2022. **SMKN 1 Cibinong** (Vocational High School). GPA 3.0. Software Engineering. 2017 - 2020.

Competition / Certificates _

All available certificates: https://bit.ly/airgg18-certs

- · Associate Data Science Competency Professional Certification (LSP Jakarta State Polytechnic 2024).
- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Hackathon 2023).
- · Web Developer Competency Professional Certification (LSP Jakarta State Polytechnic 2023). Programmer Competency
- Professional Certification (LSP University of Indonesia 2022).
- Student Creativity Program: PKM (Finalist Pass Funding 2022).
- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Best Poster 2022).
- Software Development KKNI Level 2 Competency Professional Certification (LSP SMKN1 Cibinong 2020).
- 6th/180+ Zoom Educare Program (Finalist Grade of Excellent 2019).
- 1st Place Skills Competition Bogor (LKS 2018).

Misc

- Start Learning Programming in first year vocational high school.
- Design entushiast.
- Fast self-taught, Highly adaptive, Interest to learn something new.
- Love Badminton and Traveling